One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
This weather's great!
Ne güzel hava var!
If we keep going this way, we should see the Marine base soon!
Bu yönde gitmeye devam edersek adayı birazdan görürüz!
Wow, Koby! You're incredible!
Vaay Koby! Harikasın!
We're really gonna get there?
Gerçekten hedefimize varacak mıyız?
Of course!
Tabii ki!
Sailors should at least be able to navigate!
Denizciler en azından yön bulmayı bilmelidir!
This is no time to be laughing, Luffy.
Şuan gülmenin zamanı değil, Luffy-san.
He's being held captive there.
Orada esir tutuluyor.
The infamous Pirate Hunter...
Şu meşhur Korsan Avcısı,...
Roronoa Zoro!
...Roronoa Zoro!
The man slashes up his bounties like a bloodthirsty beast.
Kana susamış bir canavar gibi ödülleri parçalayan adam...
People say he's a demon in human form!
Onun insan gibi görünen bir şeytan olduğu söyleniyor.
We're here!
Vardık! Donanma şehri!
We made it to the Marine town!
Korsanlar Kralı ve En İyi Kılıç Ustası
C-C'mon, Luffy! You can't be serious about recruiting him!
Hey, Luffy-san!
I haven't decided yet, but if he's a good guy...
Hala karar vermedim. Sadece iyi biri mi görmek istiyorum.
He was arrested because he's not a good guy!
Kötü bir adam olduğu için yakalandı!
Yum!
Mmm! Nefis!
So this Zoro guy's at the base?
Peki bu Zoro denen adam üste mi?
Maybe we shouldn't mention Zoro around here...
"Zoro" ismi buralarda tabu olmuş gibi görünüyor.
Well, let's check out the base.
Neyse, yine de üssü kontrol edelim!
You're gonna be a Marine, right?
Denizci olacaksın, değil mi?
Y-Yes... But I'm not really ready yet...
E-evet... Ama henüz hazır değilim.
This town is hilarious!
Ne eğlenceli bir kasaba!
I get Zoro, but why are they afraid of a Marine captain's name?
Zoro'yu anlıyorum, ama neden bir Donanma Albayı'nın adından korkuyorlar?
I'm getting a bad feeling about this…
Bu beni birdenbire huzursuz etti...
You sure they weren't just really excited?
Öyle eğlencesine yapmadıklarına emin misin?
That clearly wasn't it!
Kimse öyle bir şey yapmaz!
Alright! We're here!
Tamamdır! Geldik!
I finally made it!
Sonunda başardım!
I guess this is where we part ways, Luffy.
Sanırım burada ayrılıyoruz, Luffy-san.
We didn't know each other long, but...
Çok kısa bir süreydi, fakat...
Huh?
Ha?
There we go!
Gidiyoruz!
Luffy! What in the world are you doing?!
Yahu, Luffy-san! Ne yapıyorsun?!
Now, where's this demon?!
Şimdi, nerede bu şeytan?
He wouldn't be out in the open.
Böyle dışarıda olamaz.
I'm sure he's in a cell or something.
Kesin bir hücrede falandır.
Found him!
İşte orada!
Perfect!
Mükemmel!
See! There he is!
Bak! Orada!
I'm telling you! He wouldn't be out–
Açıkta olması imkan–
"Pirate Hunter" Roronoa Zoro
"Korsan Avcısı" Roronoa Zoro
A black bandana and a bellyband...
Siyah bandana... haramaki...
That's Roronoa Zoro!
Bu R-Roronoa Zoro!
It'll be easy to get him out if we untie those ropes!
Şu ipleri çözersek kolayca kaçabilir!
D-Don't be stupid! We don't know what he'd do if we set him loose!
S-Salak olma! Onu serbest bırakırsak ne olacağını kimse bilemez!
I bet he'd try to kill you, Luffy!
Eminim seni de öldürmeye çalışır, Luffy-san!
Don't worry! I'm tough!
Endişelenme! Ben güçlüyüm.
Is this guy for real?!
Bu adam ciddi mi?!
Hey, you two!
Hey, siz.
You're annoying me.
Göze batıyorsunuz.
Beat it!
Kaybolun!
Luffy! You're a goner if he joins your crew!
Luffy-san! O tayfana katılırsa işin biter!
Oh no! Luffy, you have to stop her!
Aman! Luffy-san, lütfen onu durdur!
She'll be killed!
Kendini öldürtecek!
What?
Ne var?
You must be hungry!
Aç olmalısın! Senin için biraz pirinç topu yaptım.
You got a death wish, kid? Go home!
Ölmek mi istiyorsun, ufaklık? Kaybol!
You haven't eaten a thing this whole time, mister.
Bayım, bunca zaman hiçbir şey yemedin.
Here!
Buyur! Bu benim ilk denemem, yapmak için gerçekten çok çalıştım.
I'm not hungry!
Aç değilim!
Now, stop bugging me and leave!
Hadi, beni rahatsız etme ve git!
But...
A-Ama...
I don't want them! Don't make me kick your ass!
Onları istemiyorum! Beni sinirlendirme!
Picking on little girls?
Küçük kızlara mı sataşıyorsun?
Helmeppo Captain Morgan's Son
Helmeppo Albay Morgan'ın Oğlu
You seem surprisingly well, Roronoa Zoro.
Şaşırtıcı derecede iyi görünüyorsun,...
What's with the weird guy down there?
Başka garip biri daha mı?
Thank goodness!
Şükürler olsun!
He must be with the Marines!
Donanmadan olmalı! Şimdi küçük kız güvende olacak!
Oh? Well aren't those some tasty-looking rice balls?
Oh? O pirinç topları lezzetli görünüyor.
Don't...!
Dur...!
Too sweet!
Çok tatlı!
You made them all sugary!
Bunlar şeker dolu!
Rice balls are made with salt! Salt!
Pirinç toplarına tuz koyulur! TUZ!
But I thought sweet might taste better...
Ama tatlı daha lezzetli olur diye düşünmüştüm.
Take this! And this!
Al sana! Al! Al!
Stop it! Stop it!
Yapma! Yapma!
H-How can he be so cruel?
N-Ne korkunç!
I-I worked so hard to make those...
B-Bunları yapmak için çok çalıştım...
Didn't you get the memo?
Bu duyuruyu okumadın mı?
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
"Those caught aiding criminals will be executed!
DONANMA
MARINE
Suçlulara yardım edenler
Those caught aiding
idam edilecektir!
criminals will be executed!
- Morgan
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
DONANMA
MARINE
Suçlulara yardım edenler
Those caught aiding
idam edilecektir!
criminals will be executed!
- Albay Morgan
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
DONANMA
MARINE
Suçlulara yardım edenler
Those caught aiding
idam edilecektir!
criminals will be executed!
- Albay Morgan
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
"Suçlulara yardım edenler idam edilecektir!
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
– Captain Morgan of the Marines."
– Albay Morgan."
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
- Albay Morgan
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
criminals will be executed!
idam edilecektir!
MARINE
DONANMA
Those caught aiding
Suçlulara yardım edenler
So, even the brats here know how scary Daddy can be.
Demek küçük veletler bile babamın ne kadar korkunç olduğunu biliyor!
"Daddy"?
"Babam" mı?
He must be Captain Morgan's son!
O zaman bu Albay Morgan'ın oğlu!
You. Throw the kid over the wall.
Hey, bu çocuğu dışarı at.
Sir?!
Efendim?!
I said, throw her over the wall!
Dedim ki, onu duvarın dışına at!
Got a problem following orders?
Emirlere uymak zor mu geliyor? Babama söylettirme bana!
Y-Yes, sir... Right away!
T-Tabii, efendim... Derhal!
No...
Hayır...
No!
Hayır!
Th-Thanks...
T-Teşekkür ederim.
Are you okay, Luffy?!
İyi misin, Luffy-san?!
Did you get hurt?
Yaralandın mı?
What a horrible guy...
Ne berbat bir adam.
Does anything hurt?
Bir yerin acıyor mu?
You bastard...
Pislik herif...
You sure are dead set on staying alive.
Hayatta kalmakta diretiyorsun.
Yeah! I'm gonna survive the whole month!
Evet! Bütün bir ay boyunca yaşayacağım!
Well, good luck with that.
Bol şans sana!
Only ten more days!
Geriye 10 gün kaldı.
Assuming you live that long!
Eğer o kadar uzun yaşarsan.
How can someone be so cruel, Luffy?!
Nasıl bu kadar zalim olabilir, Luffy-san?!
Huh?! He's gone?!
Ha?! Gitmiş mi?!
I hear you're a bad guy.
Duyduğuma göre kötü biriymişsin.
What are you still doing here?
Sen hala burada mısın?
Getting put out here for all to see...
Herkesin görmesi için buraya koyulmak...
Are you actually strong?
Sen gerçekten güçlü müsün?
What's it to you?!
Kendi işine bak!
If it were me, I'd probably starve to death in three days!
Ben olsam muhtemelen üç günde açlıktan ölürdüm!
Then you lack willpower.
O zaman iraden zayıf.
I will live through this...
Bunu atlatacağım!
I swear it!
Kesinlikle!
You're a pretty weird guy!
Ne garip biri.
Wait!
Bekle!
Huh?
Ha?
Could you... get that for me?
Şunu... bana verebilir misin?
You wanna eat this?
Bunu yiyecek misin?
It's more of a mud ball now.
Çamur topu olmuş.
Just shut up and give it here!
Kapa çeneni de ver şunu!
Told you so.
Söylemiştim.
It was good.
Güzeldi.
Thanks for the food.
Yemek için teşekkürler.
Really?!
Gerçekten mi?!
Yeah!
Evet! Hepsini yedi!
I'm so glad!
Çok mutlu oldum!
But then, is Zoro really as bad as they say?
Zoro gerçekten söyledikleri kadar kötü bir adam mı?
He's not!
Hayır!
After all, he let himself get tied to that cross in my place...
O bizim için kendini çarmıha gerdirdi...
Huh? What do you mean?
Ha? Nasıl yani?
It's all Helmeppo's fault.
Her şey Helmeppo'nun hatası.
He's Captain Morgan's son...
Albay Morgan'ın oğlu...
Outta the way!
Çekilin, çekilin!
Make way for my precious, adorable little pooch!
Sevimli evcil hayvanıma yol açın!
Get in the way, and you get executed!
Kim yoluna çıkarsa infaz edilecek!
No! Stop that!
Hayır! Kes şunu!
Hey, you!
Hey, sen!
You got some kinda problem with my sweet little pup?!
Evcil hayvanımla bir sorunun mu var?
Rika! Stop that!
Rika! Yapma!
We'll get in trouble!
Başımız belaya girecek!
Oh, crap!
Hass?
He's in for it now!
Şimdi yandı!
Helmeppo punches and kicks him while he's tied up!
Zoro orada bağlıyken, Helmeppo onu tekmeleyip yumrukluyor!
I... I...
Ben... Ben...
So that's what happened...
Demek öyle oldu.
I'm hungry!
Karnım acıktı! Hepimize bedavadan yemek getir!
Hey! Bring me a drink already!
Hey! Çabuk ol biraz alkol getir!
Oh, yes.
Oh, tabii ya.
To alleviate my boredom, I'll have Zoro executed tomorrow.
Çok sıkıldığım için, yarın Zoro'yu idam ettireceğim.
Save the date, everyone!
Herkes dört gözle beklesin.
Wh-What the hell are you doing?!
N-Ne yapıyorsun sen?!
Luffy! Please stop!
Luffy-san! Lütfen yapma!
This guy's scum!
Bu adam pislik teki!
Y-You hit me!
Sen... sen bana vurdun!
I'm Captain Morgan's son, you know!
Ben Albay Morgan'ın oğluyum!
So what?!
Ne olmuş?!
When I tell Daddy, he'll execute you!
Babama söyleyip seni infaz ettireceğim!
Fight me yourself!
Benimle kendin dövüş!
Luffy! Calm down!
Luffy-san! Sakin ol!
Do you want the Marines as your enemy?!
Donanmayı düşmanın yapmak mı istiyorsun?!
I've made up my mind, Koby!
Kararımı verdim, Koby!
I'm...
Zoro'yu yoldaşım yapacağım!
I am...
Ben...
great!
Mükemmelim!
Yes!
Evet! Kesinlikle haklısınız, Albay Morgan, efendim!
Then why are the recent tributes to me falling short?
Ama son zamanlarda bana gelen haraç biraz azalmadı mı?
W-Well, the citizens' wallets do have their limits...
E-eh, vatandaşların cüzdanlarının da bir limiti var...
It's a matter of respect.
Mesele bana olan saygının derecesi.
Wouldn't you agree?
Katılmıyor musun?
Daddy!
Baba!
I want you to kill someone for me!
Öldürmeni istediğim biri var!
You again? You sure have a lot of free time.
Yine mi sen? Çok fazla boş vaktin var.
I'll untie you, so come join my crew!
İplerini çözeceğim, o yüzden tayfama katıl!
Excuse me?!
Ne dedin sen?!
I'm looking for people to join my pirate crew.
Korsan tayfama katılacak insanlar arıyorum.
Forget it!
Boş versene! Bir haydut olacak kadar çaresiz değilim!
Screw that!
Unut onu!
What's wrong with being a pirate?!
Korsan olmanın nesi yanlış?!
Who'd wanna be a pirate? They're the lowest of the low!
Korsanlar aşağılıktır! Kim olmak ister ki?!
It's no big deal, right?
Oh, saçmalama!
You're already a notorious bounty hunter!
Zaten şeytani bir ödül avcısı olarak tanınıyorsun!
People can say whatever they want,
İnsanlar istediğini söyleyebilir,...
but I've never done anything I regret.
...ama pişmanlık duyduğum hiçbir şey yapmadım.
I will live through this…
Bunu da atlatacağım ve istediğim şeyi başaracağım!
Oh? I see.
Ha? Anlıyorum.
But I've already decided that you're joining my crew!
Ama ben, yoldaşım olmana karar verdim!
Like it's up to you!
Buna sen karar veremezsin!
So you're a swordsman?
Duyduğuma göre kılıç kullanıyorsun.
Yeah, but Morgan's idiot son took my gear...
Evet... Ama o aptal çocuk eşyalarımı aldı...
I'll go get it back for you!
Gidip onları senin için geri alacağım.
What?!
Ne?!
You'll get your sword when you join my crew!
Kısaca, kılıçlarını istiyorsan, yoldaşım olacaksın!
Don't screw with me!
Benimle uğraşma lan!
He's going in all by himself?!
Üssü tek başına basmayı mı planlıyor?!
Alright! Keep it steady!
Tamam, orada durun!
Stand it up in one go!
Bir çekişte ayağa kaldırın.
Daddy! Why aren't you heading out to avenge me?!
Baba! Neden intikamımı almıyorsun?
That guy hit me in the face!
O herif bana vurdu! Sen bile bana hiç vurmadın!
Do you know why I've never hit you before?
Neden sana hiç vurmadım...
Do you?
...biliyor musun?
Sure...
Şey, çünkü ben senin...
Yes.
Evet.
Because you're...
Çünkü sen...
"Axe-Hand" Morgan Marine Captain
"Balta-El" Morgan Donanma Albayı
a hopeless son who's not even worth hitting!
vurmaya bile değmeyen işe yaramaz oğlumsun!
Let's get one thing straight!
Bir şeyi açıklığa kavuşturalım!
The only great one around here is me!
Mükemmel olan senin baban! Yani ben!
By the way, I heard a rat snuck into the crucifixion yard.
İnfaz avlusuna gizlice giren bir fare olduğunu duydum.
I-I-I mean, there was that one runt, but I saw to her punishment...
E-eğer, o ufaklıktan bahsediyorsan, ben onun icabına baktım.
You killed her, I hope?
Onu öldürdün, umarım?
N-No! After all, she's still a little kid!
Hayır! Yani şey, sadece küçük bir çocuktu...
You, there!
Sen, oradaki!
Go to town and execute her!
Kasabaya git ve onu yok et!
Y-You can't mean that, sir! She's just a little girl!
Ama... o sadece küçük bir kız!
Even if it's an order...
Bir emir olsa da...
Anyone who disobeys my orders is a traitor, even little brats.
Benim emirlerime karşı gelen herkes haindir, küçük veletler bile.
B-But...
A-ama... Yapamam!
Lieutenant!
Teğmen!
Y-You didn't have to go that far!
B-bu kadar ileri gitmene gerek yoktu!
I ascended to the rank of captain with nothing but my own strength.
Beni albay rütbesine yükselten gücümdü!
Listen up!
Dinleyin! Bu dünyada rütbe her şeydir!
Captain is the top rank on this base...
Bu üsteki en üst rütbe albaydır...
And that makes me superior to everyone here!
Ve bu beni buradaki herkesten üstün kılıyor!
In other words, everything I do is right!
Bu yüzden yaptığım her şey doğrudur!
Got that, you maggots?!
Anladınız mı, sürüngenler?!
– Yes, sir! Absolutely, sir!
Evet, efendim! Kesinlikle doğru!
We can execute the brat later.
Çocuğun ölümü şimdilik bekleyebilir.
Now watch!
İyi bakın! Bu, bitmesi yıllar süren,...
The symbol of my authority!
...otoritemin simgesi!
Now, raise it up!
Şimdi, kaldırın!
Display my greatness at the apex of this base!
Büyüklüğümü bu üssün tepesinde sergileyin!
That's weird. There's no one here...
Garip. Burada kimse yok...
I gotta find that idiot son and get Zoro's sword back.
O salak oğlu bulup Zoro'nun kılıçlarını geri almalıyım.
Huh...?
Ha...?
Pull! Pull!
Çek! Çek!
You there!
Sen, oradaki!
You bumped it, didn't you?!
Sen çarptın, değil mi?!
I heard something up there...
Yukarıdan bir şeyler duydum...
I-I'm sorry, sir!
Ç-çok üzgünüm efendim! Dikkatsizlik ettim!
I told you this statue embodies me!
Size bu heykelin beni temsil ettiğini söyledim!
The slightest scratch or speck of dirt is the same as treason!
En ufak bir çizik veya kir zerresi bana ihanettir!
I'll check it out!
Bir bakayım.
Gum-Gum...
Lastik-Lastik...
Rocket!
Roket!
Now you'll pay!
Geber!
I jumped too far!
Çok uzağa zıpladım!
What is that?!
O ne?!
It flew up from below!
Yukarıya uçtu!
Got it!
Durdum!
Sorry...
Üzgünüm...
Seize him! I'll kill him myself!
Yakalayın onu! Onu kendim öldüreceğim!
– Right away, sir!
– Derhal, efendim!
Daddy! That's him! He's the guy who punched me!
Baba! Bu işte! Bana vuran adam bu!
Oh! It's you!
Oh! Sensin!
I've been looking for you!
Seni arıyordum!
Come with me! I need you to return something!
Benimle gel! Bir şeyi iade etmen gerekiyor!
Let me go!
– Helmeppo-sama!
After him! Don't let him escape!
Peşinden gidin! Kaçmasına izin vermeyin!
Captain! Someone's in the crucifixion yard!
Albay! İnfaz avlusunda biri var!
What?
Ne?
It's one traitor after another...
Arka arkaya hain çıkıyor...
You need to escape, Zoro!
Lütfen kaç, Zoro-san!
You'll be killed for doing that, you know!
Bunu yaptığın için öldürüleceksin!
I can't stand by and watch Marines act like this!
Donanmanın böyle davranmasına seyirci kalamam!
I...
Ben onurlu bir denizci olmak istiyorum!
Stop! I'm not running! In just ten more days–
Dur! Kaçamam! Sadece on gün daha–
Your execution is tomorrow!
Yarın infaz edileceksin!
What?!
Ne?!
Helmeppo never intended to honor your agreement!
Helmeppo asla sözünü tutmak niyetinde değildi.
So Luffy got angry and socked him!
Bu yüzden Luffy-san kızdı ve Helmeppo'yu yumrukladı.
He did?
Öyle mi yaptı?
And now the Marines are after Luffy.
Donanma şimdi Luffy-san'ın peşinde.
I won't ask you to be a pirate...
Senden korsan olmanı istemeyeceğim,...
but please, help Luffy!
...ama lütfen, Luffy-san'a yardım et!
He's the only one who can save you.
Seni kurtarabilecek tek kişi o.
And I think, right now, you're the only one who can save him.
Ve şu anda, onu kurtarabilecek tek kişi sensin.
Stop right there!
Dur bakalım orada!
Where's Zoro's sword?!
Zoro'nun kılıçları nerede?
I-I'll tell you! I'll tell you! Just stop dragging me!
Söyleyeceğim! Söyleyeceğim! Beni yerde sürüklemeyi bırak!
Alright! Tell me!
Tamam! Söyle!
In my room... We just passed it...
Benim odamda... Daha demin geçtik...
What? Why didn't you say so?!
Niye önceden söylemedin? Şimdi geri gitmemiz lazım.
Halt!
Kıpırdama!
Release Master Helmeppo!
Helmeppo-sama'yı bırak!
No.
Olmaz.
Shoot if you want!
İstiyorsanız ateş edin.
Move it!
Çekilin!
For the crime of treason against me,
Bana karşı ihanet suçundan...
I sentence the two of you to death!
...ikinizi de burada infaz edeceğim!
Is this the room?
Bu oda mı?
Over there!
Bingo!
But there're three of them!
Ama burada üç tane kılıç var.
Hey! Which sword is Zoro's?
Hey! Hangisi Zoro'nun kılıcı?
Oh, he passed out.
Hadi... bayıldı.
Koby!
Koby!
You've caused quite a disturbance here.
Burada ilginç şeyler yaptınız!
You and that straw hat kid are plotting a coup d'état, huh?
Siz ve o hasır şapkalı çocuk, darbe falan mı planlıyordunuz?!
I've always fought alone.
Ben hep yalnız savaştım.
Unlike a certain bastard who hides behind his terrified flunkies!
Askerlerinin arkasına saklanan senin gibi kibirli piçlerin aksine!
Roronoa Zoro...
Roronoa Zoro...
Don't you dare underestimate me!
Beni sakın hafife alma!
You may be strong, but that's meaningless before my authority!
Güçlü olabilirsin, ama benim otoritemin karşısında bir hiçsin!
Aim!
Nişan al!
I...
Ben...
can't afford to die here!
...böyle bir yerde ölemem!
Match over!
Düello sona erdi!
The winner is Kuina, with 2,000 wins and 0 losses!
Kazanan Kuina! 2,000 kez kazandı, hiç kaybetmedi!
D-Damn it...
K-Kahretsin.
You're as weak as ever, Zoro.
Her zamanki gibi güçsüzsün, Zoro.
Such a disappointment... especially for a boy.
Ne büyük hayal kırıklığı... özellikle bir erkek için.
Hey! Zoro isn't weak!
Hey! Zoro güçsüz değil!
He's the strongest guy here!
Erkek öğrenciler arasında en güçlüsü!
He can even beat grown-ups!
Yetişkinleri bile yeniyor!
But...
Ancak...
he's weaker than me.
...benden güçsüz.
Even with two swords, a weakling's still a weakling.
İki kılıçla bile olsa, güçsüz güçsüzdür.
Quit whining like little dogs.
Siz ezik köpekler çenenizi kapatmalısınız.
Another defeat, Zoro... even after you've come so far.
Bu kadar güçlendiğin halde yine kaybettin, Zoro.
Sensei!
Sensei!
Are you giving her secret training 'cause she's your daughter?!
Sırf kızınız olduğu için ona gizli eğitim mi veriyorsunuz?
Don't cheat!
Hile yapmayın!
No, no. Of course I'm not.
Hayır, hayır. Öyle bir şey yapmıyorum.
Zoro has indeed improved...
Zoro'nun güçlendiği doğru,...
but Kuina has grown stronger as well.
...ancak, Kuina da güçlendi.
Zoro?
Zoro?
Zoro...
Zoro...
I'm gonna wash my face.
Yüzümü yıkayacağım.
Damn it!
Kahretsin!
Why can't I beat Kuina?!
Niye Kuina'yı yenemiyorum?! Niye? Niye?
I'm gonna be the world's greatest swordsman!
Dünyanın en büyük kılıç ustası olacağım! E Niye?!
Zoro?!
Zoro?!
What are you doing out here?
Burada ne yapıyorsun?
Right back at you!
Onu benim sormam lazım! Bu saatte burada ne yapıyorsun?!
I'm here to challenge you to our 2,001st duel!
2001. maçımızı yapmayı teklif etmeye geldim.
I intend to make this our last fight!
Bunun bizim son düellomuz olmasını planlıyorum!
Let's end this!
Buna bir son vereceğim!
Fight me with a real sword!
Benimle gerçek bir kılıçla dövüş!
You have one, right?!
Gerçek kılıcın var, değil mi?
Against me?
Benimle mi?
Sure.
Kabul.
My 2,001st win.
2001. zaferim.
Damn it!
Kahretsin!
This sucks...
Böyle işe...
I'm the one who should be crying.
Hüsrana uğradığı için ağlayan kişi ben olmalıyım.
Huh?
He?
When girls grow up, they become weaker than men.
Kızlar büyüdüğü zaman erkeklerden güçsüz olur.
It won't be long before even you catch up to me.
Yakında sen bile bana yetişeceksin...
Zoro, you always say you'll become the world's greatest swordsman.
Her zaman dünyanın en büyük kılıç ustası olacağını söylüyorsun.
But my father said that dream isn't possible for me because I'm a girl.
Babam bana bir kızın asla öyle olamayacağını söyledi...
I understand...
Biliyorum...
I understand that's how it is!
Bunu zaten biliyorum... ama bunu kabullenemiyorum!
You're lucky, Zoro.
Zoro çok şanslısın. Sen bir erkeksin.
I want to be the world's greatest swordsman too!
Ben de dünyanın en büyük kılıç ustası olmak istiyorum!
My breasts are even starting to grow.
Göğüslerim çoktan büyümeye başladı...
If only... If only I had been born a man...
Eğer... eğer bir erkek olarak doğsaydım...
How can you cry like that after you beat me?!
Beni yendikten sonra böyle sızlanma!
It's not fair! You're my goal!
Adil değil! Sen benim hedefimsin!
Zoro...
Zoro...
Boy this! Girl that!
Erkek böyle, kız öyle!
Is that gonna be your excuse when I beat you someday?!
Bir gün seni yendiğimde, bu mu mazeretin olacak?!
You act like none of it is skill!
Yetenek önemli değilmiş gibi davranıyorsun!
You're insulting all my hard training up till now!
Yaptığım bütün sıkı çalışmayı aşağılıyorsun!
So enough of that crap!
O yüzden saçmalama!
Promise me!
Söz ver bana!
Someday, one of us will be the world's greatest swordsman!
Bir gün, birimiz dünyanın en büyük kılıç ustası olacak!
It's a race to see who makes it!
Yarışacağız ve kim olacak göreceğiz!
You dummy. You're so weak, and yet…
Seni şapşal. Çok güçsüzsün...
– It's a promise!
– Söz!
Gotta get stronger!
Güçlenmeliyim! Ki bir sürü kılıç tutabileyim!
If two's not enough, then I'll use three!
İki yetmezse, üç kullanacağım.
What do you guys want?
Neyiniz var?
Kuina...
Kuina...
Kuina's dead...
Kuina öldü...
Apparently, she slipped and fell down the storehouse steps.
Depo merdivenlerinde ayağı kaymış ve düşmüş.
The storehouse?
Depoda mı?
She was looking for a whetstone to sharpen her beloved sword.
Sevgili kılıcı için bir bileme taşı arıyormuş.
What would she need that for?
Niye öyle bir şeyi aramış?
I don't know...
Kim bilir...
She was just a child too.
Daha bir çocuktu.
Who knows why anyone does anything...
İnsanları anlayamazsın.
No one could predict something like this.
Yarın ne olacağını kim bilebilir ki?
People are... such fragile things, Zoro.
İnsanlar... çok kırılgan varlıklardır, Zoro.
Sensei...
Sensei...
That sword...
O kılıcı... bana verin.
Kuina's sword?
Kuina'nın kılıcı mı?
I'll get stronger for the both of us now!
Onun için de güçleneceğim!
I'll get so strong, my name will reach the heavens!
Adım cennete ulaşacak kadar güçlü olacağım!
I'm gonna be the world's greatest swordsman!
Dünyanın en güçlü kılıç ustası olacağım!
I promised her...
Ona söz verdim...
I...
Ben...
Very well. It's yours.
Alabilirsin!
I leave Kuina's spirit and dreams... with you.
Kuina'nın ruhunu ve hayallerini sana bırakıyorum.
Gum-Gum...
Lastik-Lastik...
Rocket!
Roket!
Fire!
Ateş!
What're you–
Sen–
Luffy!
Luffy-san!
Straw Hat?!
Hasır Şapka?!
No way...
İmkanı yok...
Nice try!
İşe yaramaz!
I told you I was tough!
Sana güçlü olduğumu söylemiştim!
Wh-Who the hell... are you?!
L-Lan... Kimsin sen?!
I'm Monkey D. Luffy!
Ben, Monkey D. Luffy.
The man who's gonna be King of the Pirates!
Korsanlar Kralı olacak adamım!